rhinomart.com 2012-06-17

# Privacy Policy

Email Privacy Policy 

We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. 

Why Did I Receive an Email From You? 

If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings. Information on how to unsubscribe to our mailings is available inside each e-mail. Alternately, you may request to be taken off our mailing list by e-mailing  sales@rhinomart.com stating that you wish to be removed.  

How is my privacy Protected? 

We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system. Our checkout process is encrypted and transmitted to us over a 128-bit SSL (Secure Socket Layer). 

Sharing and Usage 

We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information (including credit card information, e-mail address, IP address, and other personally identifiable information) with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Submitted mail addresses are only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information. 

Order Forms:
